glad to be here talk about some of the
很高兴在这里谈论一些
stuff that
那东西
is coming in spring cloud that maybe
即将来临的春天云
hasn't been talked about over and over
一直没有被谈论过
for the rest of the the conference it
在会议的其余部分
seems like I almost got a little
好像我差一点
self-conscious the other day when they
有意识的那天
kept mentioning spring cloud over and
一直在提起春天的云
over in the in the keynote but my name
在主题演讲中，但我的名字
is Spencer Gibb I work for pivotal on
是Spencer Gibb，我致力于
spring cloud
春天的云
I joined specifically to start spring
我专门加入以开始春天
cloud with with Dave sire it's been a
与戴夫（Dave）父亲在一起，
little more than a year we announced
一年多一点，我们宣布
spring clouds at spring one in Dallas
在达拉斯的春天一春天的云
last year yeah that's pivotal that's us
去年是关键的是我们
and we've we've been it's been exciting
而且我们一直都很开心
to work on it to try and add some some
努力尝试并添加一些
more features and we'll hopefully get to
更多功能，我们希望能够
talk a little bit about some of those
谈一些
and delve a little deeper and I'm happy
再深入一点，我很高兴
to answer any questions that that I can
回答我可以回答的任何问题
so if I don't don't respond just yell
所以如果我不回应就大喊
and all Walter Walter we'll try and get
和所有沃尔特·沃尔特我们将尽力
your questions questions answered so
您的问题回答的问题
when we started spring cloud as we were
当我们像以前一样开始春天的云时
working on it we discovered some
在工作上，我们发现了一些
concepts some some abstractions that we
概念一些我们抽象的
we created as we started working on it
我们在开始工作时就创建了
one of those is service registration and
其中之一是服务注册，
discovery
发现
another is distributed configuration a
另一个是分布式配置
control bus which in in my mind for
在我看来，控制总线
those of you familiar with spring boot
那些熟悉Spring Boot的人
and actuator the control bus to me is
执行器到我的控制总线是
kind of like a distributed actuator so
有点像分布式执行器
rather than acting on an individual note
而不是按个别音符行事
at a time you can act on on multiple
一次您可以对多个
nodes and then some some cluster
节点，然后是一些集群
primitives that some of the other folks
其他一些人的原始人
had had come up with like leader
曾想过像领导者
election and locks so in our initial
选举和锁定，所以在我们最初的
release
发布
we've since started a release train
从那以后，我们开始了发行培训
naming so it wasn't originally called
命名，所以它最初不是
angel but we kind of renamed it though
天使，但我们有点改名了
in our original release that the release
在我们的原始版本中
train names are tube station names in
火车名称是地铁站名称
London Dave's from London and so he you
伦敦戴夫来自伦敦，所以他你
picked something near and dear to his
在他亲爱的附近挑选了一些东西
heart we went with with Netflix Eureka
与Netflix Eureka一起工作的心
for our service discovery and
为了我们的服务发现和
registration we have let's see we do
注册，让我们看看我们
have a Netflix employee here John
约翰有一位Netflix员工
Schneider if you want to raise your hand
施耐德，如果你想举手
so and the collaboration has been fun
所以合作很有趣
with with Netflix on that for
与Netflix合作
distributed configuration we they hadn't
他们没有的分布式配置
open sourced their their configuration
开源他们的配置
server but we we did something in a
服务器，但我们在
similar vein if you've heard other talks
如果您听过其他演讲，也很相似
too backed by git or subversion source
太受git或subversion源支持
control we created a bus based on
控制我们创建了基于
RabbitMQ and we didn't have a release of
RabbitMQ，我们没有发布
the the cluster implementation so just
集群的实现
the other day what day is today Thursday
前几天星期四是星期四
I think it was Tuesday night I posted a
我认为是星期二晚上，我张贴了
blog post to the spring bio website
到Spring Bio网站的博客文章
announcing the first milestone of
宣布...的第一个里程碑
Brixton which is the next version in our
布里克斯顿，这是我们的下一个版本
in our release train some of the things
在我们的发布训练中，有些事情
that have been added to Brixton that
被添加到Brixton
I'll try and is the focus of the talk
我会尽力而为，成为演讲的重点
today
今天
besides upgrades to the Netflix stack
除了升级到Netflix Stack
the Netflix version of spring cloud
Netflix版本的Spring Cloud
we're going to talk about console from
我们将从
hashey Corp who's anyone familiar with
熟悉的hashey Corp
with console if you're not familiar with
如果您不熟悉，可以使用控制台
console how about vagrant so same guys
控制台如何关于流浪汉
Mitchell Hashimoto and and company so
桥本美切尔（Mitchell Hashimoto）和公司
we'll talk a little bit about that
我们会谈一点
Pachi zookeeper will also talk a little
Pachi动物园管理员也会讲一点
bit about tracing and our spring cloud
关于跟踪和我们的春天云
sleuth some cluster implementations and
侦听一些集群实现和
a little bit about sed from from core OS
关于核心操作系统的sed
which is not in the release it's an
这不是发布中的
incubator project so we started with
孵化器项目，所以我们从
with Eureka for service discovery and
与Eureka一起进行服务发现和
registration it's highly available they
注册是高度可用的
built it to to scale to handle I don't
建立它来按比例缩放以处理我不
want to say the wrong number but
想说错号码，但是
hundreds if not thousands of instances
数百个（如果不是数千个）实例
of services that are available to to the
可用于
Netflix team it it prefers to hand a
Netflix团队更喜欢
client data even if it's if it's stale
客户数据，即使是过时的
so it's it's highly it's ap and the cap
所以它的高度是ap和上限
theorem it has some long thresholds for
定理它有一些长的门槛
registration and cache refreshing so
注册和缓存刷新，因此
that includes ribbon which is the load
包括丝带的负载
balancing client so sometimes it takes a
平衡客户端，因此有时需要
minute or two before you see a new
一两分钟后，您会看到一个新的
instance that has been added and it's
已添加的实例，它是
certainly been battle tested right this
肯定是经过战斗测试的
is one of the reasons we picked Netflix
是我们选择Netflix的原因之一
to start because of the they just pound
开始，因为他们只是一磅
it and and it it has handled many
它并且它已经处理了许多
failures and works well for a Netflix so
失败，并为Netflix运作良好，因此
that's that's where we started but I was
那就是我们开始的地方，但是我当时
already on my radar before I even joined
在我加入之前就已经在我的雷达上
the company where some of these other
这些其他一些公司
some of these other technologies and
其中一些其他技术，以及
when we started the project even if it
当我们启动项目时，即使它
wasn't a goal originally in my mind I
本来不是我心目中的目标
wanted spring cloud to kind of behave
想要春天的云表现出来
like the spring data project for example
例如 spring data 项目
you know that has support for relational
你知道有关系的支持
databases and key value stores and
数据库和键值存储以及
column stores and and network did you
专栏商店和网络您
anyway so I I
反正二
wanted to kind of be like that so so I
想成为那样，所以我
had started playing with some of these
开始玩其中一些
other technologies and looking at
其他技术并关注
implementations other implementations of
实现的其他实现
registration and and configuration so
注册和配置如此
for our we had a I talked a little bit
为了我们，我们聊了一点
about our our config server its
关于我们的配置服务器
stateless we use the bootstrap phase
无状态，我们使用引导阶段
that spring cloud has introduced to a
春天的云已经引入了
spring boot app to load configuration
Spring Boot应用程序加载配置
data from an external source and then to
数据从外部来源，然后
start into the normal application
开始进入正常应用
context lifecycle of an application so
应用程序的上下文生命周期
we built that in and put the this
我们将其内置并放入
bootstrap phase into a common project
引导阶段进入普通项目
spring Cloud Commons so that it could be
春天的云共享，以便它可能是
reused we we built the bus originally on
再利用，我们最初在
on rabbit so our only implementation
在兔子上，所以我们唯一的实现
worked on RabbitMQ and and that was one
在RabbitMQ上工作，那是一个
of the sticking points with me is that I
我的症结所在是我
I didn't like that it was specific to a
我不喜欢这是特定于
message broker implementation we have a
消息代理实现，我们有一个
couple of endpoints actuator endpoints
几个端点执行器端点
that we added to be able to refresh the
我们添加以能够刷新
context of a number of instances at once
一次实例的上下文
or to change the local spring
或改变当地的春天
environment so to start who's sort of
环境，以便开始谁是那种
zookeeper I would assume a lot of people
动物园管理员，我想很多人
have so it's it's a part of the Apache
有它是Apache的一部分
foundation it's a consistent distributed
基础是一致的分布式
coordination server when you ask what
协调服务器，当您问什么
zookeeper is it's it's kind of hard to
动物园管理员，这很难
wrap your head around you could say it's
缠住你的头，你可以说这是
it's useful for configuration well you
这对配置很好很有用
could say it's it's it's Service
可以说是服务
registration well you could say you
注册好你可以说你
could do locks with well you can do lots
可以做得很好，你可以做很多
of these things right but in the end it
这些事情是正确的，但最终
is something that can keep state in a
是可以保持状态的东西
clustered way
集群方式
it started life as a Hadoop sub project
它从Hadoop子项目开始
so out of that to try and help
所以要尝试帮助
coordinate Hadoop clusters so it's it's
协调Hadoop集群就可以了
fairly old compared to the rest of the
相较于其他
technologies that we're looking at John
我们正在研究约翰的技术
do you know when Eureka started okay so
你知道尤里卡什么时候开始好吗
so even got a few years on on Eureka and
所以甚至在尤里卡上花了几年时间
lots of companies use this for various
许多公司将其用于各种
technologies and one of the reasons I
技术，也是我的原因之一
wanted to look at zookeepers because
想看动物园管理员，因为
just because of that lots of companies
只是因为有很多公司
already have zookeeper as part of their
已经有动物园管理员作为他们的一部分
stack in fact Netflix uses it not for
实际上，Netflix不将其用于
service discovery and registration but
服务发现和注册，但是
they have it as part of their their
他们将其作为自己的一部分
stack in fact they have open sourced
实际上它们已经开源了
they donated curator to the Apache
他们向阿帕奇捐赠策展人
foundation which is a fabulous client
优秀客户的基金会
library that spring cloud zookeeper
那个春天的图书馆云动物园管理员
actually takes advantage of as well as
实际上利用以及
exhibitor which is a zookeeper sidecar
参展商是动物园管理员的小汽车
process that that helps keep it alive
有助于保持生命的过程
and and do some other things that
并做其他一些事情
facilitate running a zookeeper cluster
促进运行Zookeeper集群
so zookeeper config uses the
所以zookeeper设定使用
hierarchical store to store
分层存储
configuration it like I said it uses
就像我说的那样使用
curator ID there's a there's an issue to
策展人ID有一个问题
add support for exhibitor exhibitor
增加对参展商的支持
allows the when the state of the
允许状态为
zookeeper cluster changes it allows it
Zookeeper群集更改允许
to dynamically update the members of the
动态更新
cluster so to be a little more highly
集群，以便更高一点
available so we one of the things that's
可用，所以我们要做的事情之一
interesting about spring boots
spring boot 很有趣
configuration is it loads properties
配置是否加载属性
files in a specific order right there's
文件以特定顺序存在
a in config server that you can have
您可以拥有的配置服务器
application amyl or properties which
应用戊基或具有哪些特性
gets loaded by every application then
然后由每个应用程序加载
you could have application - some spring
你可以申请-一些春天
profile like applique
轮廓像贴花
Devore application - prod and then you
Devore应用程序-产品然后您
can have a specific named properties
可以具有特定的命名属性
files just for a specific type of
文件仅用于特定类型的
application and and zookeeper
应用程序和动物园管理员
configuration we mimic that hierarchy
我们模仿该层次结构
even though there aren't individual
即使没有个人
files right in zoo keeper you store the
文件直接在您存储的动物园管理员中
individual properties on their own so we
单独的属性，所以我们
also have zookeeper service discovery so
也有动物园管理员服务发现
I had started we used the the there's a
我已经开始使用了
recipe from from curator for discovery
策展人的发现食谱
our friends at for finance out in Poland
我们的朋友在波兰寻求融资
also did something similar and so they
也做了类似的事情，所以他们
donated some of their work to spring
春季捐献了一些作品
cloud they've been very very interested
云，他们一直非常感兴趣
in spring cloud and have done some some
在春天的云里，做了一些
significant contributions to spring
对春季的重大贡献
cloud zookeeper in space specifically
专门在太空中的云动物园管理员
and they were excited for this release
他们对此发布感到兴奋
so they can start to integrate and and
这样他们就可以开始整合并
migrate to spring cloud zookeeper and
迁移到Spring Cloud Zookeeper并
eventually be running spring cloud
最终将运行春云
zookeeper in their production
动物饲养员
environments there's no bus
没有公共汽车的环境
implementation there probably could be
实施可能有
but when I asked my colleagues about it
但是当我问我的同事
they they strongly suggested against
他们强烈建议反对
riding a bus implementation in in
乘坐公交实施
zookeeper so let's see it let's see if
动物园管理员，让我们看看吧，看看是否
we can actually make this run
我们实际上可以进行此运行
close those down to make sure I don't
关闭那些，以确保我不
bring my laptop just to a to a crawl see
把我的笔记本电脑拿来抓
that alright so I have on a Mac it's
没关系，所以我在Mac上
super easy to get zookeeper just brew
超级容易让动物园管理员酿造
install zookeeper if I recall correctly
如果我记得正确，请安装Zookeeper
so it started yay
所以开始了
so I can come look in the so by default
所以我可以默认进入
we put configuration in the config
我们将配置放在配置中
directory and you can see that there is
目录，您可以看到有
a directory for an application named
名为的应用程序的目录
test zookeeper app and it has some
测试zookeeper应用，它有一些
properties in it so if I come to tell AJ
属性，所以如果我来告诉AJ
all right so here is this is the sample
好的，这是示例
application in that I've that is in the
我已经在
spring cloud zookeeper project for those
春季云动物园管理员项目
of you familiar with this this is a
你们这很熟悉
spring boot application pretty standard
spring boot 应用程序相当标准
all of spring cloud is built on top of
所有的春天云都建立在
spring boot we take Vantage heavily of
spring boot ，我们非常重视Vantage
the Auto configuration and actuator and
自动配置和执行器
the general and the configuration
一般和配置
properties from from spring boots so it
弹簧靴的特性，因此
we we really take advantage of a spring
我们真的可以利用春天
boot so this is a spring boot
靴子，所以这是一个 spring boot
application you can see I use that
应用程序，你可以看到我用
enable discovery client from our Commons
从我们的下属启用发现客户端
project and what happens is that
项目，发生的是
depending on the implementation of the
取决于实施
discovery client in this case zookeeper
在这种情况下的发现客户端Zookeeper
it will read Auto register the
它会显示自动注册
application and set it up so that you
应用程序并进行设置，以便您
can discover other services running and
可以发现其他正在运行的服务，
I'll just show look the will we have a
我只想看看我们会不会
little mapping that says I'm going to
说我要去的小地图
start multiple instances myself and it
自己启动多个实例
will just cycle through I'm going to be
会一直循环下去
a client of my myself just so we can see
我自己的客户，所以我们可以看到
the load balancing via ribbon actually
实际上通过功能区进行负载平衡
so one of the things that's interesting
所以有趣的事情之一
is that ribbon is a Netflix project it's
那个功能区是一个Netflix项目吗
client side load balancer we have
客户端负载均衡器
support for that it's been cloud Netflix
支持它是云Netflix
but ribbon we have support it works
但是功能区我们有支持
across all these different
跨越所有这些不同
implementations by plugging in a server
通过插入服务器来实现
list that is specific to this discovery
特定于此发现的列表
client so this load balancer client is a
客户端，因此此负载均衡器客户端是
ribbon load balancer so I'm going to go
功能区负载平衡器，所以我要走了
ahead and I'm not hello hmm so I'm going
向前，我不是你好，嗯，我要走了
to start a couple of these
开始其中的几个
really quick
真快
I'm hit this endpoint so I'm just
我击中了这个终点所以我只是
returning the the server that's the the
返回的服务器
object that's returned from the load
从负载返回的对象
balancer client and you can see that I
平衡器客户端，您可以看到我
got myself on port 8081
使自己进入端口8081
but if i refresh that it's just cycling
但如果我刷新那只是骑自行车
through so both of these were registered
通过这样，这两个都被注册
if I go to that's funny okay don't know
如果我去那很有趣，好吧，不知道
why that says it's down it's working and
为什么那说它失败了，为什么？
so you can see that there are some
所以你可以看到有一些
services registered in in with the
在中注册的服务
zookeeper discovery client also if I
Zookeeper发现客户端，如果我也
look at the env actuator endpoint you
看看环境执行器的端点
can see that I loaded some properties
可以看到我加载了一些属性
out of out of zookeeper we wanted to
从动物园管理员出来
make sure that we I decided that that
确保我们决定
the hierarchy in zookeeper would be
在动物园管理员的层次结构将是
translated into the dot notation that
转换成点表示法
that spring boot expects so if I look at
spring boot 期望如此，如果我看看
in the CLI at these properties
在CLI的这些属性中
Oh
哦
I get this guy
我得到这个人
so this is the value that's in there and
所以这就是其中的价值
you can see that this key hierarchical
您可以看到此键是分层的
key path translated into config slash
关键路径翻译成配置斜杠
attesa tsuki / app info dot description
attesa tsuki /应用信息点说明
ok so fairly straightforward translation
好的，非常简单的翻译
and allows you to individually set set
并允许您单独设置
those those properties one of the nice
那些属性是不错的之一
things about the curator client it has
关于策展人客户的事情
built-in retry similar to the Eureka
类似于Eureka的内置重试
client so I could have started this and
客户，所以我本来可以开始
not had zookeeper up and the app would
没有动物园管理员，该应用程序会
have happily run it wouldn't obviously
快乐地运行它显然不会
been able to connect to the other
能够连接到另一个
services or other services connect to it
服务或其他服务连接到它
but as soon as zookeeper came up it
但是一旦动物园管理员出现
would have connected which is which is a
本来可以连接的是
really really nice feature of curator
策展人真的很棒
let's see if there's anything else to
让我们看看是否还有其他需要
show with zookeeper
与动物园管理员一起表演
I think that's any questions about
我认为这是关于任何问题
zookeeper before we we move on to the
动物园管理员，然后我们继续前进
next so next up is console like I said
接下来，接下来是我说的控制台
from Hoshi Corp creators of vagrant nice
来自Hoshi Corp的vagrant nice的创作者
things about console is that it is by
关于控制台的事情是
default it is multi data center aware
默认情况下，它支持多数据中心
you can be running so console is a you
您可以运行，所以控制台就是您
run a cluster of console servers and
运行控制台服务器集群，并
there are no masters or slaves they have
他们没有主人或奴隶
the concept of a server and an agent but
服务器和代理的概念，但是
the the server cluster itself is is
服务器群集本身是
masterless uses a peer-to-peer gossip
无主使用点对点八卦
system that that hash carp created
hash鱼创建的系统
called surf which in and of itself is is
所谓的冲浪本身就是
pretty slick console leans a little more
漂亮的控制台更加倾斜
towards having consistent data but you
拥有一致的数据，但是您
can actually tune it there are three
实际可以调整到三个
different ways you can tell console to
告诉控制台的不同方法
retrieve data and we'll get into those
检索数据，我们将深入探讨
but it is tunable the agent the way they
但是代理可以通过他们的方式进行调整
describe
描述
use it runs as a sidecar to your
使用它作为您的辅助工具
application so it's really nice because
应用程序，所以真的很好，因为
all the the default localhost 8500
所有默认的本地主机8500
should probably be what you're
应该就是你
connecting to anyway you just would run
连接到您将要运行的任何地方
the agent right next to every every
每个旁边的代理商
instance of an application so it's
应用程序的实例，因此
really really nice and they have a slick
真的非常好，而且光滑
little web-based UI that I will show you
我将向您展示的基于Web的小界面
you'll get a demo of so they had one of
您将得到一个演示，因此他们有一个
the things that console comes with is a
控制台附带的东西是
a key value store and they have a very
一个关键值存储，他们有一个非常
nice so what it so zookeeper you need a
很好，所以它需要什么样的动物园管理员
client library to connect to it and with
客户端库连接到它并与
console everything is available via a
控制台一切都可以通过
REST API very nice very clean REST API
REST API非常好非常干净的REST API
and so the key value HTTP API is what we
所以关键值HTTP API是我们
use to store store properties it looks
用于存储外观的属性
very similar to zookeeper right it's a
非常类似于动物园管理员，这是一个
hierarchy of directories and values and
目录和值的层次结构以及
again we mimic the same order that I
再一次，我们模仿我的顺序
showed you with with zookeeper what is
向动物园管理员展示了什么
different about console is that service
控制台的不同之处在于该服务
registration and discovery is baked into
注册和发现被纳入
console right it's not a recipe built on
控制台，这不是建立在配方上的
top of it they it's a first-class
最重要的是，它是一流的
citizen and there are API specifically
市民有专门的API
for service discovery nice very nice
用于服务发现很好非常好
HTTP API an interesting thing is that it
HTTP API有趣的是，它
also runs a DNS server so for legacy
还运行DNS服务器，因此对于旧版
applications that you can't change to
您无法更改的应用程序
use consuls nice HTTP API if you can set
如果可以设置，请使用领事不错的HTTP API
up the machines that they're running to
他们正在运行的机器
use console as its DNS server and be
使用控制台作为其DNS服务器并
able to resolve services via via DMS so
能够通过DMS解决服务，因此
they've they thought about legacy and
他们曾经考虑过遗产
the ability to use DNS to
使用DNS的能力
connect to these other services and
连接到这些其他服务，并
there's a rich health check system built
有一个丰富的健康检查系统
into the service registration and
进入服务注册并
discovery
发现
just about anything you could think of
几乎所有您能想到的
that you wanted to check you can do it
您想检查一下就可以做到
it you can run whatever script on the
它可以运行任何脚本
system you want it and it would check it
您想要的系统，它将对其进行检查
if you look at the documentation it's
如果您查看文档，它是
it's pretty pretty amazing what you can
您可以做的非常令人惊讶
do with it by default since a lot of
默认情况下使用它，因为很多
these applications we write our rests
这些应用程序我们编写其余部分
http/2 based applications they have the
基于http / 2的应用程序具有
concept of an HTTP health check and we
HTTP健康检查的概念，我们
automatically register the actuator
自动注册执行器
health endpoint as an HTTP health check
运行状况端点作为HTTP运行状况检查
with with console they also have an
与控制台，他们也有一个
event system that is built in that
内置的事件系统
allows you to send kind of ephemeral
允许您发送短暂的
event messages to these non persistent
这些非持久性事件消息
messages to all of your instances and I
给您所有实例和我的消息
have built the bus implementation of
建立了总线的实现
that which as I was prepping for the
我为之准备的
demo for some reason is broken but
演示由于某种原因被破坏，但是
that's okay because we're anyone go to
没关系，因为我们有人去
the spring cloud stream talk so you can
春天的云流谈话，所以你可以
see here it says we use a spring
看到这里说我们用弹簧
integration well Dave sire last night
昨晚Dave父亲的整合很好
finished rewriting the bus to use stream
完成重写总线以使用流
which is independent of the message
与消息无关
broker which is awesome so now I need to
经纪人，这太棒了，所以现在我需要
do is translate what I had written using
要做的就是翻译我写的东西
spring and Gration to have a console
Spring和Gration有一个控制台
spring cloud stream message broker and
春季云流消息代理和
then so I won't be able to show the bus
那我就不能看巴士了
because it's it's broken right now but
因为它现在坏了，但是
but I will get it working but it's nice
但我会让它工作，但是很好
because now if you can connect to
因为现在如果您可以连接到
localhost 8500 excuse me
本地主机8500对不起
you get all of these pieces served up by
您会得到所有这些碎片
one system configuration service
一项系统配置服务
discovery and the bus they also have a
发现和公共汽车，他们也有一个
nice ACL system that they are starting
他们开始的不错的ACL系统
to integrate deeper and deeper into the
越来越深入地融入
system so your configuration B could be
系统，因此您的配置B可能是
controlled by an ACL service
由ACL服务控制
registration is starting so you have to
注册已经开始，所以您必须
be authorized to be able to register a
被授权能够注册
service for example but they'll be
服务，但他们会
extending that to so that you must be
扩展到您必须
authorized to be able to see the
被授权能够看到
instances of registered services for
的注册服务实例
example that's coming question so why
这个问题即将来临的例子，为什么
would you use console versus Eureka that
你会使用控制台还是Eureka
is a good question so one of them is
是一个很好的问题，所以其中之一是
since console is not JVM based and it
因为控制台不是基于JVM的，所以它
runs as an agent if your system is
如果您的系统是作为代理运行
polyglot this might be an option that
多语言这可能是一个选择
you want to take advantage of because of
你想因为
the rich HTTP API so that's one one
丰富的HTTP API，所以这是一个
question excuse me got a little scratch
问题对不起，我有点scratch
in my throat this is my third talk so
在我的喉咙里，这是我的第三讲
the legacy DNS support is another one
旧版DNS支持是另一种
thanks for leading me into my next slide
感谢您带领我进入下一张幻灯片
by the way and being able I the the I
顺便说一句，我能够
like being able to just say if I if I
喜欢能够说我是否
can reach my local agent I get access to
可以联系我可以访问的本地代理
the system and the agent is responsible
系统和代理负责
for contacting the rest of the the
用于联系其余的
cluster the behavior is different than
集群的行为不同于
Eureka right Eureka is built for this
尤里卡对尤里卡为此而建
highly available infrastructure console
高可用性基础架构控制台
is is geared a little more towards
更适合于
consistency I think the ACL system in
一致性我认为ACL系统在
council is is something that that when
理事会是当
Eureka was built right it was built for
尤里卡（Eureka）建于
you know our walled garden inside
你知道我们里面的围墙花园
there's no one else it's not
没有人不是
multi-tenant you know when we added
当我们添加时，您知道多租户
Eureka to if anyone saw the spring cloud
尤里卡到如果有人看到春天的云
services talk in this room the other day
服务有一天在这个房间里聊
you know we had to on top of Eureka add
你知道我们必须在尤里卡上面添加
some security for some of our customers
为某些客户提供一些安全保障
who wanted you know didn't want other
谁想要你知道不想别人
even of their systems to be able to see
甚至他们的系统也能够看到
what's registered for example but you'll
例如注册了什么，但您会
in a future version of console that will
在将来版本的控制台中
happen where you wouldn't you know you
发生在你不认识你的地方
not even authorized so I think the ACL
甚至没有授权，所以我认为ACL
system is also a neat feature of console
系统也是控制台的简洁功能
hey all right let's see it let me
嘿，好吧，让我看看
yeah
是的
so John's pointing out that Netflix did
所以约翰指出Netflix
create a sidecar and we actually kind of
创建一个边车，我们实际上是
said ah I bet we could do something like
说啊，我敢打赌，我们可以做点什么
that and it took me about half an hour
那花了我大约半个小时
and there's spring cloud Netflix sidecar
还有春天的云Netflix边车
so polyglot isn't the only way to do it
所以说多语不是唯一的方法
in console it just is more first-class
在控制台上，它更一流
in console than the sidecar right you'd
在控制台中，而不是您需要的小推车
have to run the Java side car for
必须运行Java边车
polyglot support for Eureka so but it is
对Eureka的多语种支持，但事实是
there just a different focus is all
那里只是一个不同的焦点
thanks for pointing that out so let me
感谢您指出这一点，所以让我
run let me turn off I don't want to
运行让我关闭我不想
overload my laptop by that by the end
最终使我的笔记本电脑超载
with having all these systems running on
在所有这些系统上运行
it so I'm gonna start console up and
所以我要启动控制台
then so I'm gonna show you the UI to
然后，我将向您展示UI
begin with so this is one of the neat
首先，所以这是整洁的之一
things about console so it's it's up it
关于控制台的事情就这样了
sees itself as one of the services that
认为自己是服务之一
is registered and it has the just the
已注册，并且具有
the cluster status available you can see
您可以看到可用的群集状态
into the key value store that is
到键值存储中
available a little while ago I went
前段时间我去了
ahead and added a few properties already
前面并已经添加了一些属性
I'll show you that but super easy to to
我会告诉你，但超级容易
come in and you know change values and
进来，你知道改变值，
edit things it's it's really really nice
编辑的东西真的很好
nice little UI has about the ACLS which
一个不错的小用户界面，关于ACLS
we've disabled because I haven't turned
我们因为我没转身而被禁用
them on and if there were it's another
他们在，如果有另一个
data center it knows how to contact that
知道如何联系的数据中心
as well
以及
so really really nice UI that comes with
所以附带的界面真的非常好
with console so now let me show you the
与控制台，所以现在让我向您展示
the code here
这里的代码
ahead and stop these
提前停止这些
so again simple spring boot application
所以还是简单的Spring Boot应用程序
with that enable discovery client and
与启用发现客户端和
this application looks almost identical
该应用程序看起来几乎相同
to the the one I showed you in zookeeper
我在动物园管理员给你看过的那个
right I have the load balancer client I
对，我有负载均衡器客户端
also injected the discovery client here
也在这里注入了发现客户端
so let me run a couple of these as well
所以让我也运行其中的几个
I come back to the map
我回到地图
again you can see it's using ribbon to
再次，您可以看到它正在使用功能区
cycle through just like like before and
像以前一样循环
zookeeper but now if you go to the UI
Zookeeper，但现在如果您进入用户界面
I shouldn't have closed that you can see
我不应该关闭你可以看到的
that I now have this service registered
我现在已经注册了此服务
the test console application if I go to
测试控制台应用程序，如果我去
that you can see I have two instances of
可以看到我有两个实例
it running each with a an HTTP health
它以HTTP运行状况运行每个
check running on it so very nice now
检查运行它现在非常好
you'll also notice if I go back to the
您还会注意到，如果我回到
services that I registered the spring
我注册春季的服务
boot management with this so right now
现在就启动管理
there's a limitation in in Eureka one
尤里卡有一个局限性
that only allows you to register one
只允许您注册一个
service per JVM but console doesn't have
每个JVM服务，但控制台没有
that restriction and Eureka two won't
那个限制和尤里卡两个不会
either but you're able to register
都可以，但是您可以注册
whatever ports that your application
您的应用程序的任何端口
might be listening on right by default
默认情况下可能在正确收听
usually it's just the HTTP port but if
通常只是HTTP端口，但是如果
you have with you can run the spring
有了春天就可以奔跑
boot management an actuator on a
引导管理
different port right or if you spin up
正确的其他端口或者您向上旋转
another you can spin up your own
另一个你可以自己动手
internal you know ports if you had some
内部的，你知道港口，如果你有一些
TCP thing that you're doing
您正在做的TCP事情
you can certainly register it with with
您当然可以向进行注册
console as well so very nice and let's
控制台也非常好，让我们
come back here and I can show you the
回到这里，我可以告诉你
the environment so this is a nice demo
环境，所以这是一个不错的演示
because you can see the hierarchy of
因为您可以看到
properties right so this test property
属性正确，因此此测试属性
is available to all applications yes
适用于所有应用程序
so so these good questions what was the
所以这些好问题是什么
first one history of edits so so no so
第一个编辑历史，所以不是这样
so so one thing to point out these are
所以要指出的一件事是
not using the configuration server right
不使用配置服务器的权利
these are using a local client to
这些正在使用本地客户端
connect instead of using our spring
连接而不是使用我们的弹簧
cloud config server the local
云配置服务器本地
configuration clients go directly to
配置客户端直接转到
these services so we don't have git or
这些服务，所以我们没有git或
anything versioned like that I'm not as
像我这样的版本
familiar with zookeeper I know it keeps
熟悉动物园管理员，我知道
a version but I don't know if it keeps
一个版本，但我不知道它是否保留
the history of that particular yeah I've
是的，我曾经的历史
seen that so there's a there are tools
看到有一个工具
that do that but by default these
做到这一点，但默认情况下这些
applications don't have a history like
应用程序没有类似的历史记录
git does which is why we picked get for
git这样做是为什么我们选择get
one of those things the other he
其中一件事情他
mentioned encryption right keys that
提到加密权密钥
that like so we have that facility built
这样，我们已经建立了设施
into the config server to encrypt so I
进入配置服务器进行加密，所以我
have a pull request and if I would have
有拉取请求，如果我愿意
had enough time I could have showed you
有足够的时间我可以告诉你
but another console another hashey core
但是另一个控制台是另一个hashey核心
product is called vault
产品称为保险库
it's job is to store keys and secrets
它的工作是存储密钥和秘密
and go figure it has backends for
并考虑它有后端
zookeeper console and sed so that would
Zookeeper控制台并执行sed操作
be the direction I would go for storing
就是我要存放的方向
secrets and those particularly at all
秘密，尤其是那些秘密
three of those
其中三个
uh-huh so so we have one of the things
嗯，所以我们有一件事情
that you can't leave Mike by former
你不能离开迈克
coworker I can't ease it so you can
同事我无法放松，所以你可以
there's there's a couple of things one
有两件事
of the things is we have added a refresh
事情是我们增加了刷新
actuator endpoint on the with the bus
总线上的执行器端点
that you could say hey refresh all of
你可以说嘿刷新所有
instance all of services of type X and
实例所有类型为X的服务
they would go back out and refresh their
他们会回去刷新他们的
configuration so you could go make the
配置，以便您可以进行
edits and then say hey go go update so
编辑，然后说嘿去更新
that would be based so based on the
这将基于
properties of the particular server
特定服务器的属性
right so if they contact you so there's
对，所以如果他们与您联系，那么
with zookeeper and console there's not
与动物园管理员和控制台没有
they would get whatever is is considered
他们会得到任何被认为是
consistent for that system does that
对于该系统而言，一致
make sense
说得通
I I don't know if you can edit multiple
II不知道是否可以编辑多个
properties at the same time in zookeeper
在Zookeeper中同时设置属性
or console so there's no I don't I don't
或控制台，所以没有我不我不
know if you can actually do that at the
知道您是否真的可以在
same time you'd have to make two
同时你必须做两个
separate edits that make sense but those
有意义的单独编辑，但那些
wouldn't reflect immediately if you
如果您不能立即反映
write because your clients wouldn't have
写因为你的客户没有
that the other thing you
那另一件事你
so with console and zookeeper unlike
因此，与控制台和Zookeeper不同
config server we are I think in
我认为的配置服务器
zookeeper we've added at the the ability
我们添加了此功能的Zookeeper
to watch the repository and the client
观看存储库和客户端
can automatically refresh well his
可以自动刷新他的
question was I've updated one value and
问题是我已经更新了一个值，
well that depends on that depends on
取决于，取决于
your platform right so anyway yeah so I
您的平台正确，所以无论如何，是的，我
hope it's clear as clear as mud
希望它像泥一样清晰
yeah yes and I would have to investigate
是的，我必须调查
I don't know if you can change two
我不知道你能不能换两个
values at once and want either of those
一次获得价值，并希望其中任何一个
system in atomic manner I'm not I'm not
系统以原子方式我不是我不是
sure if you could it wouldn't be a
确定如果可以的话不会
problem so
这样的问题
Eureka is where zookeeper and console
尤里卡是动物园管理员和控制台的地方
lean towards consistency
趋于一致
Eureka leans towards availability right
尤里卡倾向于可用性
so it will give you stale data rather
因此它将为您提供陈旧的数据
than not be consistent where these are
比在这些地方不一致
less likely to do that okay so that's
这样做的可能性较小，所以
that's one of the big differences
那是最大的差异之一
between these these systems which is one
这些系统之间是一个
of the reasons Netflix built it the way
Netflix建立方式的原因
they did because when they scale to tens
他们这样做是因为当它们扩展到数十
of thousands of machines running they'd
数千台正在运行的计算机
rather have the data available even if
宁愿有可用数据，即使
it's old they also they have multiple
很老，他们也有多个
layers of protection say you get a stale
几层保护说你过时了
server right one that doesn't even exist
服务器权甚至不存在
anymore especially in AWS with ribbon
尤其是在具有功能区的AWS中
you have a layer of protection with with
您可以通过
retries historic Cebu and do a fallback
重试历史悠久的宿雾并进行后备
if you fail again so there are multiple
如果您再次失败，那么会有多个
layers to deal with that specifically
专门处理的层
with with that so great question okay I
带着这么大的问题好吧，我
can't show you the bus because it's
无法向您展示巴士，因为
busted but at least it happened before
破灭，但至少它发生在
the demo and it wasn't live on stage any
演示，没有在舞台上直播
more questions about console before I
在我之前有更多关于控制台的问题
move on how're we doing with with time
继续说我们如何与时间在一起
when is this session end I guess
我猜这个会话什么时候结束
whatever we want cuz it's the last one
无论我们想要什么，因为这是最后一个
when's it supposed to end started at
它应该什么时候开始于
2:15 thank you all right
2:15好的，谢谢
any more questions questions are great
还有更多问题，问题很棒
even if I don't know the answers
即使我不知道答案
so his question was could you use config
所以他的问题是你可以使用配置
server that we had already released with
我们已经发布的服务器
service discovery from console the
从控制台发现服务
answer is absolutely right so each one
答案是绝对正确的，所以每个人
of these pieces that I've talked about
我谈论的这些作品中
is available via starter and you can
可通过启动器使用，并且您可以
pick and choose now like I said I think
就像我说的那样，现在就选择
that's one of console strengths is that
控制台的优势之一是
it has all of these things but you could
它拥有所有这些东西，但是你可以
certainly mix and match you know like I
当然可以像我一样混合搭配
said config server already has the the
说的配置服务器已经有
encryption part built in but like I said
内置加密部分，但就像我说的
I have a pull request for fault that
我有一个过失要求
that could be merged in before Brixton
可以在布里克斯顿之前合并
ghost GA so yep
鬼GA如此
any other questions let's see we got
还有其他问题，让我们看看
next
下一个
okay anyone heard of a vet CD before
好吧，以前有人听说过兽医CD
this is by core OS they make an
这是通过核心操作系统，他们使
operating system that has built for
专门为
containers it's used heavily in their
容器，它们在他们的
their distributed their distributed
他们的分布他们的分布
system again it's very similar to
系统再次非常类似于
consult a zookeeper
咨询动物园管理员
that's a distributed key-value store
那是一个分布式键值存储
it's written and go has a nice little
它写了，走了一个不错的小
CLI it has a nice HTTP API has a ton of
CLI它有一个不错的HTTP API，
language bindings for it this is a an
语言绑定，这是一个
incubator project so the github
孵化器项目，所以github
repository is spring cloud incubator
仓库是Spring Cloud孵化器
with dashes in between each we're anyway
无论如何我们之间都有破折号
it's incubator will decide or maybe the
它是由孵化器决定还是
community will decide whether whether
社区将决定是否
they want us to to release this and
他们希望我们释放这个
support this so again there's kind of
支持这一点，再次有一种
repeating myself here it seems like but
在这里重复自己似乎
spring cloud config at CD uses their
CD上的Spring Cloud配置使用它们的
HTTP API again look yeah hey look at
HTTP API再看一次，嘿，看一下
that
那
I get it we're gonna go edit this live
我明白了，我们要去现场直播
how's that what was that what the
那是怎么回事
question is what am I using to do my
问题是我在做什么
slides so it's it's a combination of
幻灯片，这是它的组合
things
东西
the the rendering of it the JavaScript
JavaScript的渲染
and I use a open source product product
我使用开源产品
called reveal Jas I my content is in
我的内容在
markdown so very easy to write what I'm
降价很容易写下我的意思
using to watch like that made that go
习惯看着那样使
live by just me saving the file this
靠我自己保存文件
this will end up on my personal website
这将最终出现在我的个人网站上
under the presen but is called Hugo go
根据介绍，但被称为雨果去
Hugo dot IO it's a static site generator
雨果点IO这是一个静态网站生成器
and it will watch your source and
它将监视您的来源并
refresh your page for you when when it's
刷新页面时，
done so thanks for forgiving me so
这样做，谢谢你原谅我
config very similar to console very
配置非常类似于控制台
similar to sed we get the same kind of
与sed类似，我们得到了相同的
loading order so you can have properties
加载顺序，以便您可以拥有属性
that are available to every application
适用于每个应用程序
some specific to your application or
一些特定于您的应用程序或
just or your application in a specific
公正或您的特定应用
profile and so this is one of the
配置文件，所以这是其中之一
reasons that this is still an incubator
仍然是孵化器的原因
project is discovery so lot lots of
项目被发现很多
people use that CD for discovery but
人们使用该CD进行发现，但是
there is no specific support for
没有特定的支持
discovery in sed all right with
sed中的发现可以
zookeeper I was able to use the curator
动物园管理员，我能够使用策展人
recipe and it made my life really really
食谱，这让我的生活变得非常真实
easy to do it you know a few API calls
容易做到，您知道一些API调用
and I was done so whatever is here I
我做完了，所以无论我在这里
came up with and it might not be ideal
想出了这可能并不理想
so that's one of the reasons it's it's
这就是它的原因之一
still an incubator project
仍然是一个孵化器项目
so we use the HTTP API and we set a node
所以我们使用HTTP API并设置一个节点
with a time to live
有时间生活
that's configurable but when that time
这是可配置的，但是那时
to live expires the whoever's contacting
居住的人过期
sed to find that you know an instance
sed发现您知道实例
that that instance would be gone so what
该实例将消失，那又怎样
I do is I set up a little background
我要做的是我设置了一些背景
thread and I just continually refresh
线程，我不断地刷新
that node setting the appian so that the
该节点设置了appian，以便
TTL resets itself again it's a pretty
TTL再次重置自己，这很漂亮
simple system and it works but that's
简单的系统，它的工作原理，但这是
probably one of the reasons why why it's
可能是为什么它的原因之一
still in a so if you're interested and
如果您有兴趣，还可以
want to learn and maybe you could do
想学习，也许你可以做
something better than I could this would
比我能做到的更好的东西
be a place to do a pull request without
成为没有请求的地方
pull requests by the way we love the
以我们喜欢的方式提出要求
community that's one of the reasons
社区，这是原因之一
actually like working a pivotal on the
实际上就像在
open source side because my my customers
开源方面，因为我的客户
are you guys pretty awesome so let's see
你们真的很棒吗，让我们看看
if I can get this working
如果我能做到这一点
so I have some convenient scripts in
所以我有一些方便的脚本
spring cloud console and Etsy D to just
Spring Cloud Console和Etsy D
start up after you have it installed
安装后启动
just just just to start it up for you
只是为了为您启动
where am i showing code unfortunately
我在哪里显示代码很不幸
this is going to look very similar to
这看起来非常类似于
the last two sample applications that
最后两个示例应用程序
you got fact if I were going to be
你有事实，如果我要
really tricky I could have written one
我本来可以写一个真的很棘手
sample application and used maven
示例应用程序和二手Maven
profiles to bring in the right
配置文件带来合适的
dependency and the sample out the same
依赖性和样本取出相同
sample application could work regardless
示例应用程序可以正常工作
of what was underlined because of the
因为
boots Auto configuration right I mean I
靴子自动配置对，我是说我
have copies of these applications in
在这些应用程序中有副本
each repository but it could have been
每个存储库，但可能是
one and we just swap out to discovery
一个，我们只是交换去发现
the starter and it just uses the other
入门，它只是使用另一个
one so that's it's me being lazy I guess
一个，就是我很懒
that I just copy
我只是复制
so again right this I mean could be the
所以再次对，我的意思是可能是
same application I've just opened it up
我刚刚打开过的同一应用程序
three different times the the properties
三个不同时间的属性
are different right so we've got a
是不同的权利，所以我们有一个
little bit of time so the things that we
一点时间，所以我们
set up in the properties and I've just
在属性中设置，我只是
been using all the defaults or you know
一直在使用所有默认值，或者您知道
what path in this hierarchy should the
该层次结构中的哪个路径应该
configuration go where should the
配置去哪里
discovery go what should I register as
发现去我应该注册什么
the IP address of this service or the
该服务的IP地址或
hostname and should I use the IP address
主机名，我应该使用IP地址吗
or the host name what's that
或主机名是什么
time-to-live that I I talked about how
II谈到的生存时间
often should I go update that that node
我应该经常去更新那个节点
right you don't want the Refresh to be
对，您不希望刷新
greater than the time to live anyway so
大于生活的时间，所以
let's go ahead and again start me a
让我们继续，再次开始我
couple of these
其中几个
and I can show you here it's not out of
我可以在这里告诉你这并非没有
completing for me so I have a property
为我完成，所以我有财产
already set up I need to get that guy
已经设置好了，我需要找那个家伙
show you the value so this little CLI is
显示您的价值，所以这个小的CLI是
really nice to be able to just set
能够设置真的很棒
values get values so we could also see
值获取值，所以我们也可以看到
what's in what was the default there for
什么是那里的默认值
that cloud discovery
那个云发现
so here you can see that there is the
所以在这里您可以看到
the the note the directory if you want
如果需要，请注意目录
to call it that as the name of the
称它为
application and you see there are two
应用程序，您会看到有两个
values one for each instance okay and
为每个实例设置一个值好，并且
that's that's literally all I'm doing
那就是我要做的全部
I'm doing there let's see if and I just
我在那边，让我们看看是否，我只是
put the the host and port in there so
将主机和端口放在那里
that when the discovery client actually
当发现客户端实际
goes out to get those values it has them
出去获取那些有价值的东西
to report back so just a soup I mean
报告回来，所以我只是说汤
this could be you know some complex JSON
这可能是您知道一些复杂的JSON
object with a lot more than host import
具有比主机导入更多的对象
if we wanted right just really really
如果我们真的想要正确的话
simple for now
现在很简单
same thing Ribbon knows how to get get
功能区也知道如何获得
through them we can go look at the
通过他们，我们可以去看看
environment and here we have that same
环境，在这里我们有相同的
hierarchy except it's from from a TV
层次结构，但它来自电视
okay so let's see what would it look
好吧，让我们看看会是什么样
like if I wanted to say I don't want my
就像我想说我不想我
I want a different value from my
我想要与我不同的价值
property right so let's set so instead
财产权，所以我们将其设置为
of for every application I want it to be
对于每个应用程序，我都希望成为
for my application so via here right so
对于我的应用程序，所以通过这里就可以了
now let's sorry apologize for that I'm I
现在，对不起，我很抱歉
can see it just fine I don't know what's
可以看的很好我不知道是什么
wrong with you guys 82
你们错了82
so refresh is one of the actuator
所以刷新是促动器之一
endpoints that that I mentioned before
我之前提到的端点
the that spring cloud provides let's see
春天的云所提供的让我们来看看
if this worked we should see a new value
如果成功了，我们应该看到一个新的价值
in this property source there we have it
在此属性源中，我们拥有它
right so I updated my properties without
对的，所以我没有更新我的属性
restarting the server question
重新启动服务器问题
sure so the question is kind of back to
可以肯定的是，问题又回到了
that you know paper trail who submitted
你知道谁提交的论文线索
who changed what value when right
谁在正确的时候改变了什么价值
so in general with these we don't really
所以总的来说，我们并没有真正
have a solution for that from the
有一个解决方案
application side it just gets the values
在应用程序端，它只是获取值
from whatever source it does right with
从任何合适的来源
config server you have a little better
配置服务器你要好一点
story right in the the because of the
的故事，因为
version control system that backs it
支持它的版本控制系统
yeah sure but that's the the well what
是的，但是那很好
he's talking about is well is is the
他说的很好是
opposite the view from the client which
与客户的看法相反
versions of the data which versions of
数据的版本
the configuration do I have and well no
我有没有这个配置
so so one of the things that actuator
所以致动器的一件事
does is is if your keys end in password
就是如果您的密钥以密码结尾
or key or something like that it starts
或键或类似的东西开始
them out already so we we take care of
他们已经出来了，所以我们照顾
that already that that does happen we do
确实已经发生了
trigger offense when when refresh
刷新时触发攻击
refresh has happened so there's a
刷新发生了，所以有一个
potential that you could do something
您可能会做某事的潜力
based on that event right but yeah
基于该事件，对，但是
that's that's actually a good idea
那实际上是个好主意
I'd have to I'd love to log an issue and
我不得不记录一个问题，然后
have a discussion about that in general
对此进行一般性讨论
because that particular we don't have a
因为那个特别的我们没有
solution for that in general right from
一般的解决方案
the client side what version of these
客户端这些是什么版本的
things do I have but
我有东西，但是
so Netflix has a tool called EDA that
因此Netflix有一个称为EDA的工具
that does some some logging of when
记录一些时间
things change in the environment to know
事物在环境变化中才知道
that so that yeah there there could be a
这样，是的，那里可能有一个
something similar done for specifically
专门做了类似的事情
for configuration right yes
对于配置权是
yep yeah yeah John just making the point
是的，是的，John提出了要点
that yeah this stuff shouldn't be
是的，这个东西不应该是
changed that often and not by an
经常改变而不是改变
operator at runtime usually so yes good
通常在运行时是运算符，所以不错
points and that's right you know one of
要点，没错，您知道其中之一
the reason one of the things even with
原因之一甚至
config server there's no security built
配置服务器没有建立安全性
into it right but you take spring
正确，但是你需要春天
security and you add whatever you need
安全性，您添加所需的任何内容
to so you know you shouldn't let just
到所以你知道你不应该只让
anyone do that but you're right that's a
任何人都这样做，但你是对的，这是一个
great great point
好极了
so some other versions of discovery that
所以发现的其他一些版本
we have created if anyone's heard of
我们创建了，如果有人听说过
lattice this is our easiest way to call
这是我们最简单的呼叫方式
it a single tenant dumbed-down Cloud
它是单个租户愚蠢的云
Foundry that you can run on your laptop
可以在笔记本电脑上运行的Foundry
you can run it in AWS and we built a
您可以在AWS中运行它，我们构建了一个
simple version of discovery that uses
使用的发现的简单版本
the receptor api from the diego
来自迭戈的受体api
component of cloud foundry so it's a
云铸造的组成部分，因此
read-only discovery client right
只读发现客户端权限
registration happens at the platform
注册发生在平台上
level when you when the platform creates
平台创建时的水平
a new instance of the service it's
服务的新实例
immediately available to all the other
立即可供其他所有人使用
services ok and we have some spring
服务还可以，我们有一些春天
cloud connectors for some simple data
云连接器，用于一些简单数据
services and messaging services and
服务和消息传递服务以及
lattis as well there's another one I
lattis也有我一个
didn't mention Josh long also created a
没提乔希很久也创造了一个
version for Cloud Foundry using the
版本的Cloud Foundry使用
Cloud Foundry API very very similar to
Cloud Foundry API非常类似于
this except using the Cloud Foundry
除了使用Cloud Foundry之外
api's again read-only I know one of the
api再次只读，我知道其中之一
developer advocates for Google wants to
Google的开发者倡导者希望
do a discovery client for kubernetes I
为kubernetes做一个发现客户端
think so would be similar to these using
认为与这些使用类似
its API so one of the new things coming
它的API，所以即将出现的新事物之一
in brixton is called spring cloud
布里克斯顿的春天云
cluster these are some concepts that
这些是一些概念
that distributed systems sometimes try
分布式系统有时会尝试
and deal with that our
并处理我们的
not always easy to to implement but
并非总是易于实施，但
distributed locking and leader election
分布式锁定和领导者选举
there are implementations of leader
有领导者的实现
election with zookeeper and I have a
与动物园管理员选举，我有一个
pull request in for console following
向控制台拉入请求
their their guide on their website and a
他们在他们的网站上的指南和
distributive lock using using Redis you
使用Redis进行分布式锁
could also do that with with zookeeper
也可以和动物园管理员一起做
and and with console as well this this
和控制台以及这个
will has reached milestone and will be
将达到里程碑，并将
available this project actually came out
这个项目实际可用
of the work that they had done with the
他们所做的工作
guys have done with spring XD when XD in
XD在
the the original version had a managed a
原始版本中有一个托管的
container and so it was started to be a
容器，所以它开始成为一个
platform and so they needed to be able
平台，所以他们需要能够
to say to provide high availability
说提供高可用性
who's the master admin and so this is
谁是主管理员，所以这是
comes out of that work I believe there's
从这项工作中我相信
also an implementation of some of these
也是其中一些的实现
patterns in Hazel cast that they did ok
榛树中的图案投射出它们还不错
I'm not gonna demo that no look at that
我不会演示不看那个
I already listed all those great you
我已经列出了所有很棒的你
could do some something similar that's
可以做一些类似的事情
one of the things that people use sed
人们使用sed的一件事
for for for locking I'm gonna show
对于锁定，我要证明
something else that isn't on my slides
我的幻灯片上没有的其他内容
how's that so one of the things that was
那是怎么回事
demoed last night in the keynote was
昨晚在主题演讲中降级的是
they showed the Zipkin UI so we have a
他们展示了Zipkin UI，所以我们有一个
new project
新项目
called spring cloud sleuth sloth sleuth
叫春云探秘懒惰探秘
what this is is a yes there's nothing
这是一个是没有什么
really exciting to see here yet but so
看到这里真的很令人兴奋，但是
spring cloud sleuth is our project to
Spring Cloud Sleuth是我们的项目
start to deal with distributed tracing
开始处理分布式跟踪
some of the original code donated again
再次捐赠了一些原始代码
from by for finance they had a simple
从财务上他们有一个简单的
solution of putting a they called it a
把一个解决方案，他们称之为
correlation ID into just into the logs
相关ID刚进入日志
so that every log statement had some ID
这样每个日志语句都有一些ID
that later on in in log stash or or some
以后在日志存储中或
other log aggregation system you could
您可以使用的其他日志聚合系统
start to search and see things and it's
开始搜索并看到事物，这是
grown from there we incorporated we're
从那里成长，我们成立了我们
trying to come up with a nice
试图拿出一个不错的
abstraction to incorporate other systems
合并其他系统的抽象
including Zipkin so Adrian if you under
包括齐普金，所以阿德里安（Adrian）
age a the siz Adrian Cole who has just
年龄只有
started to work how long has it been two
开始工作已经有多长时间了
to three weeks something like that with
三个星期之类的
with the spring cloud open-source team
与Spring Cloud开源团队一起
he's he used to work at Twitter he'd he
他曾经在Twitter工作过
also used to work at Netflix so he's got
也曾经在Netflix工作，所以他有
some great experience he's coming to
他来的一些很棒的经验
help us work on this distributed tracing
帮助我们进行这种分布式跟踪
problem and correlation and he he's one
问题和相关性，他是他的一员
of the you know I call you one of the
你知道我叫你之一
founders of opens is the open Zipkin
Opens的创始人是Open Zipkin
organization there's organizers yeah so
组织那里的组织者是的
yeah the project he does not a founder
是的，他不是创始人的项目
of the project just the open
该项目只是开放
implementation of maintenance of Zipkin
实施Zipkin维护
so or were we're certainly happy to have
所以或者我们当然很高兴拥有
him have him here with us and so there's
他有他在我们这里，所以有
there's not a lot to see in this project
这个项目没什么可看的
but what happens is that we we start to
但是发生的是我们开始
instrument
仪器
different places in the application to
在应用程序中的不同位置
either start a trace generate a trace ID
要么启动跟踪，要么生成跟踪ID
and span IDs so this is a lot of these
和范围ID，所以这是很多
terminologies are based on the the
术语基于
google the dapper project from google
谷歌从谷歌dapper项目
they put out a white paper and so it's
他们拿出白皮书，所以
real easy to use their terminology but
真正易于使用的术语，但
span a trace is follows some particular
跨度跟踪是一些特定的
pathway throughout your whole system
整个系统的途径
from the original client request to
从原始客户请求到
whatever downstream systems it talked to
与之交谈的任何下游系统
and there are segments of that trace
并且有该迹线的段
which we call which are called spans so
我们称之为跨度
we start to instrument different places
我们开始测量不同的地方
in the code either using the hooks that
在代码中使用钩子
spring provides or in other places where
春天提供或在其他地方
they're not aren't hooks we can use AOP
它们不是钩子，我们可以使用AOP
to hook into those places where they're
迷上他们所在的地方
not hooks by default but we start to
默认情况下不挂机，但我们开始
propagate these IDs throughout the
将这些ID传播到整个
system so that they can be fed to some
系统，以便他们可以喂一些
downstream system and you can get this
下游系统，你可以得到这个
picture of what a particular request
特定请求的图片
looked like so we yes question
看起来像所以我们是问题
saysay yeah so so whenever there is a
说的是的，所以只要有一个
change in in thread we try and propagate
我们尝试传播的线程变化
that context through through the
通过
different threads a particular problem
不同的线程一个特定的问题
we're having is with with history right
我们拥有与历史的权利
now the circuit breaker which runs
现在运行的断路器
things in a thread pool but yes that's
线程池中的东西，但是是的
what we try and do is propagate those
我们尝试做的是传播那些
values across whatever boundary
跨越任何边界的价值
you know we encounter whether that's a
你知道我们遇到的是不是
thread in the current JVM
当前JVM中的线程
it's an HTTP request to some other
这是对其他一些HTTP请求
subsystem sure
子系统确定
in the yeah let me let me show you so
是的，让我让我向你展示
let me start my little sample
让我开始我的小样本
application
应用
this one does even less than those other
这个比其他的做得更少
applications well so oh it failed
应用程序很好，所以它失败了
I have to
我必须
yeah so so I'm running Zipkin the
是的，所以我正在运行Zipkin
components of Zipkin which are a
Zipkin的组成部分是
collector query service and the web UI
收集器查询服务和Web UI
so just one second it looks like we're
所以只有一秒钟
good my sample is specific to Zipkin so
好，我的样本特定于Zipkin，所以
it expected them to be to be up and
它期望他们会起来，
running but
运行但
so you can see these beautiful colored
这样你就可以看到这些美丽的彩色
logs right I have this these empty
正确的日志我有这些空的
values because I haven't made a request
值，因为我尚未提出要求
yet right so there's nothing to to trace
没错，所以没有什么可追踪的
but if I come hit my sample application
但是如果我来打我的示例应用程序
which did something just like my other
跟我的一样
app it made a call to myself so I'm
应用程序打了个电话给自己，所以我
gonna have some I I can show you the
会有一些II可以告诉你
code it's easier to show you them then
代码，然后向您展示它们会更容易
not so when I hit slash I got me a
并非如此，当我打斜线时，我得到了一个
little random time just so that my trace
一点随机的时间只是为了我的踪迹
looks interesting and I just called
看起来很有趣，我刚刚打电话给
myself but a different endpoint of
我自己，却是
myself that I've implemented down here
我自己，我已经在这里实施
and just returned returned the value so
刚返回就返回了值，所以
just a little simple two-stage call I
只是一个简单的两阶段通话
come back to my run logs you'll start to
回到我的运行日志，您将开始
see trace IDs so you can see that they
查看跟踪ID，以便您看到它们
all have the same trace ID
都具有相同的跟踪ID
even though but the different span IDs
即使但跨度ID不同
once for one for each section right one
每个部分一次，一次正确
for the original request to slash which
对于原始要求大幅削减
you can actually see here in some of the
您实际上可以在这里看到一些
values right so this particular one was
正确的价值观，所以这个特殊的是
to slash where this one was to slash hi
砍到这个要砍的地方
- okay so you can start to see those and
-好的，这样您就可以开始看到这些内容了
if I look at the how I added that
如果我看看我是如何添加的
so this takes advantage of a new feature
所以这利用了新功能
in spring boot 1.3 which allows you to
在Spring Boot 1.3中，您可以
specify the log pattern the properties
指定日志模式的属性
so this could go in configuration it
所以可以在配置中
could write the B so it could be the
可以写B，所以可能是
same for everything you have and we add
一切都一样，我们添加
just a simple simple value to the SL f4j
对SL f4j而言只是一个简单的简单值
I don't even know what MDC stands for
我什至不知道MDC代表什么
but that's where you you add it to the
但这就是您将其添加到
logging context and it will show right
记录上下文，它将显示正确
so we we that was what was donated from
所以我们我们那是捐赠的
for finance their implementation of that
为其实施提供资金
for us okay so there's there it is in
对我们来说好吧，所以那里有
the event log in the logs yes but but
事件日志在日志中是，但是
wait there's more for just five dollars
等一下，五美元就够了
more you get a picture so so this is
更多你得到一张照片，所以这是
those same values were shipped to Zipkin
这些相同的值被运送到Zipkin
which stored them in Redis and then
将它们存储在Redis中，然后
allows us to use this very clunky ugly
让我们可以使用这个笨拙的丑陋
UI from from Zipkin to to look at the
从Zipkin到使用者介面
traces that were just done so you can
刚刚完成的跟踪，以便您可以
see I'm the only app will go ahead and
看到我是唯一可以继续使用的应用程序，
find the traces you can see I tested
找到可以看到我测试过的痕迹
this a couple hours ago but here's the
这是几个小时前，但这是
trace that we just we just did and so
跟踪我们刚才所做的事情，如此
you can see that the the originating
您可以看到原始的
request to HTTP slash is here and the
HTTP斜线的请求在这里，
subsequent request HTTP 2 is below it
后续请求HTTP 2在其下方
and we give you you can click in and see
我们给你，你可以点击进入
a little more details and we're one of
多一点细节，我们是其中之一
the things we're starting to do is to
我们开始做的事情是
try and that Adrian is organizing is to
尝试，阿德里安正在组织是
try regardless of implementation there
尝试不管在那里执行
are companies all over the place trying
各地的公司都在尝试
to do some
做一些
our types of things and it would be
我们的事情类型，这将是
really really nice if there was some
如果有的话真的很棒
kind of community agreement on what
关于什么的社区协议
those things looked like and how they
这些东西看起来如何，它们如何
were shaped so that regardless of the
的形状使无论
actual implementation that you happen to
您碰巧的实际实现
be using you can reason about them in a
正在使用，您可以在其中对它们进行推理
similar manner right so one of those is
类似的方式，所以其中之一是
are these attributes that you see here
这些是您在此处看到的属性
posted via HTTP we also have some
通过HTTP发布我们也有一些
instrumentation for spring integration
弹簧集成仪表
so if you send a message to a queue we
因此，如果您将邮件发送到队列，我们
can show you some information about that
可以向您显示一些相关信息
message for example in these traces so
例如在这些跟踪中的消息
and here I'm sampling everything that's
在这里，我将采样所有
another term is sampling how often do
另一个术语是采样频率
you want this data to be captured and
您想要捕获这些数据，
we're saying 100 percent of the time
我们说的是100％的时间
which you can see the amount of
您可以看到的数量
information for these two little calls
这两个小电话的信息
right that's a lot there could be a very
对，可能很多
high explosion of data so you want to
大量数据爆炸，因此您想要
determine some way of sampling some
确定一些采样方式
percentage of your data or turning it on
数据百分比或启用
for particularly or your user or a
特别适合您或您的用户或
particular set of users or when
特定的一组用户或何时
someone's having a problem anyway so
反正有人有问题
there's lots of strategies for when to
何时有很多策略
actually capture this data versus all
实际捕获这些数据与所有数据
the time which we're doing in these
我们在这些中所做的时间
samples so here first good
样品所以这里首先好
so who's talking about the value that is
所以谁在谈论价值
created by the Cloud Foundry router a
由Cloud Foundry路由器创建
request ID there there isn't support for
不支持的请求ID
that now but we the gentleman that
现在，但我们先生
seated right in front of you you need to
坐在你前面
have a conversation with and we should
与我们交谈，我们应该
right there should be especially in
对，尤其应该在
Cloud Foundry that we should have some
Cloud Foundry我们应该有一些
way to get whether that's a an attribute
获取这是否是属性的方法
like I've showed these HTTP attributes
就像我展示了这些HTTP属性
so you can you can search by these
所以你可以通过这些搜索
attributes so you'd be able to search by
属性，以便您可以通过
that whether that's the actual trace ID
那是否是实际的跟踪ID
or not you should be able to correlate
还是应该您能够关联
between them if it's not but we should
他们之间，如果不是，但我们应该
definitely talk about it in fact the
肯定是在谈论它
trace should probably start at the
跟踪可能应该从
router not when it hits the app so
路由器没有击中应用程序，所以
that's another thing so
那是另一回事
yes so his question was maybe at some
是的，所以他的问题也许在
point during my request I'm splitting
在我的请求中点
and it's not a it's not a single path
这不是一个单一的路径
through the system it's there's multiple
通过系统，有多个
paths through the system and if how do
系统中的路径以及如何执行
we account for that so your your
我们考虑到这一点，所以您的
question was right they will have the
问题是正确的，他们将有
same trace ID but different span IDs
相同的跟踪ID但不同的跨度ID
this particular UI might not handle that
这个特定的UI可能无法处理
situation perfectly but we want to get
情况完美，但我们想得到
to the point where whatever however we
到了无论如何我们
display them would work like that
显示它们将像那样工作
because as soon as you start having
因为一旦你开始拥有
messaging right that isn't no longer
不再不再具有消息权
even synchronous right and we have some
甚至同步权，我们都有一些
demos of that in that in in the spring
在春季的演示
cloud sleuth repo there is a messaging
云侦探仓库有一条消息
sample you can see some of that in
样品，您可以在其中看到一些
action so great question yeah we
行动如此重大的问题，是的，我们
definitely want that to be a first class
绝对希望成为一流
citizen in tracing
公民追查
sorry there's just explaining that that
对不起，只是在解释说
sometimes these fans in in very large
有时，这些粉丝人数众多
systems can can reach 100 to 200 spans
系统可以达到100到200个跨度
for one trace and there are some
一丝痕迹，还有一些
facilities in the UI to kind of zoom in
使用者介面中的便利设施
on little pieces of it but yeah they can
在它的一小部分上，但是的，他们可以
get quite long yes absolutely so
相当长，是的，所以绝对
question was could we have the tracing
问题是我们能否进行追踪
being put into the logs even though it's
被放入日志，即使它是
not being shipped off to some log
没有被运送到一些日志
collection place and that don't think we
收集的地方，认为我们不
have support for that right this minute
这分钟有支持这项权利
but that's definitely seems like
但这肯定看起来像
something that you might want to do is
您可能想做的是
always logged but sometimes ship to to
始终记录，但有时发送到
your trace collection system
您的跟踪收集系统
so for those who couldn't hear he was
所以对于那些听不到他的人
describing how it had it's useful to
描述它如何有用
always have sampling on but at Twitter
总是有样品但在Twitter
where he came from they they throttled
他来自哪里，他们节制了
it by right rate as opposed to just a
它以正确的速率而不是一个
percentage of fusers or something like
热熔器或类似的百分比
that if I can sum up and make small so
如果我可以总结并缩小
awesome any more questions I think so I
我认为还有其他很棒的问题
when this gets to my website that this
当这到达我的网站时
link here in the middle you'll be able
链接到中间，您将能够
to follow those those links to some some
跟随那些链接到一些
of the material out on the internet that
互联网上的材料
I found trying to compare and contrast
我发现试图进行比较和对比
some of the discovery and configuration
一些发现和配置
systems yeah
是的
if you anybody have any other questions
如果您还有其他问题
I think I'm go go ahead
我想我要继续前进
so he's asking if there's any problem
所以他问是否有问题
having a different clock times and if
有不同的时钟时间，如果
it's been a solved problem hopefully the
希望这是一个已解决的问题
ceiling is not going to following us I
天花板不会跟随我们
would say there has been attempts to
会说有尝试
solve the problem I don't think it's
解决我不认为的问题
totally solved one thing that is is that
完全解决了一件事就是
each span keeps the local time of when
每个跨度保持当地时间
it was sent and received even in verses
它甚至在经文中也被发送和接收
the log file so so the spans have their
日志文件，这样跨度就可以了
time stamps associated with them so
与它们相关的时间戳
you'd be able to get them relative to to
您将能够使他们相对于
each other right so that's something
彼此都对，这就是
where we're looking at right because
我们正在寻找正确的地方，因为
especially when you get into the
特别是当你进入
asynchronous tracing write some message
异步跟踪写一些消息
that got kicked off that doesn't fit
开始不适合的
well into a timed and so trying to come
很好的时机，所以试图来
up with a strategy for relative time not
制定相对时间策略
necessarily timestamp right this one
一定要在这个上加盖时间戳
happened before this one so one of the
发生在这一个之前
another concept that I didn't really
我不是真的一个概念
mention was that of a parent span so
提到的是父母跨度
when you create a new span so say you've
当您创建新跨度时，说您已经
kicked off to something else one thing
揭开序幕
that happens it says oh I'm my parent is
碰巧它说哦，我是我的父母
this guy so there is a little bit of the
这个家伙，所以有一点
relative when it happened even if their
亲戚什么时候发生，即使他们
time stamps overlapped because you know
时间戳重叠，因为您知道
that he was your parent you he would
他是你的父母，他会
have to come after you even if the time
即使有时间也要跟着你
stamps weren't quite right so so there's
邮票不太正确，所以有
been a little work into that but it's
做了一些工作，但这是
not totally solved more questions
尚未完全解决更多问题
right right yeah yep yeah yep
正确正确是是
go I'm sure
我确定
yeah yep that's yeah yep so he's saying
是的，是的，所以他说
that you can with config server by
您可以通过配置服务器
default you use config server to find
默认情况下，您使用配置服务器来查找
discovery Netflix the default is the
发现Netflix，默认值为
other way you use discovery to find
您使用发现来查找的其他方式
config server and that feature is only
配置服务器，该功能仅
specifically for config server is
专门用于配置服务器是
currently only available in in Eureka
目前仅在尤里卡可用
yep so and go ahead and log an issue in
是的，继续并在中记录问题
is it in console that you're using
是在控制台中使用的吗
yeah I mean I like I said we'll have to
是的，我是说我喜欢我说我们必须
me yeah yeah it's me
我是的是我
yeah and and there are there are a
是的，那里有一个
couple other things that aren't quite
加上其他不太完全相同的东西
there so Zul works across should work
在那里，祖尔的工作应该可以工作
across all of these ribbon does there
跨越所有这些功能区
was something that was missing that I
是我所缺少的东西
know is missing besides that so thanks
除此之外，我们还不知道
for bringing that that uh-oh turbine
带来那个呃涡轮
doesn't work with the other discovery
不适用于其他发现
systems yet so any other questions
系统还有其他问题
yep that's the it's so he's mentioning
是的，就是这样，他提到
brave which is the library that we use
勇敢的，这是我们使用的图书馆
to write to Zipkin in spring class Luth
在春季班Luth给Zipkin写信
not sure brave is agnostic to the
不确定勇敢是否不可知
framework you're using so so yeah it
您正在使用的框架，所以是的
does have some core libraries it's been
确实有一些核心库
migrated to open Zipkin so that I can't
迁移到开放的Zipkin，所以我不能
Chris what's his name the maintainer
克里斯维护者叫什么名字
yeah
是的
yes which is
是的，那是
yes
是
so yeah if you want to to chat with us
是的，如果你想和我们聊天
we're on getter a spring cloud supreme
我们正在吸气至尊
cloud and opens ooking slash zipping
云并打开oking斜杠拉链
we don't know yet yeah
我们还不知道
yeah and and with spring clouds sleuth
是的，并与春天的云彩侦探
our goal is to instrument spring apps to
我们的目标是对spring应用进行检测
have that instrumentation happen
有仪器发生吗
regardless of what your downstream
不管你下游
tracing solution happens to be right so
跟踪解决方案恰好是正确的
we've we have Zipkin we have the logs
我们有Zipkin我们有日志
but we could certainly we want to play
但是我们当然可以玩
nice and so that's we're trying to get
很好，这就是我们想要得到的
that that right and Adrian's trying to
那个权利和阿德里安（Adrian）试图
drive the community from the the open
从开放中带动社区
Zipkin side and just tracing in general
Zipkin方面，只是一般的追踪
with the community they're having a
与社区一起，他们正在
summit I don't know what it's called
顶峰，我不知道这叫什么
workshop a tracing workshop in San
在San举办寻人工作坊
Francisco in October it's something like
十月的弗朗西斯科
that where people from from all over the
来自世界各地的人们
community from Twitter to SoundCloud to
从Twitter到SoundCloud的社区
others are pivotal of course but they're
其他人当然是关键的，但他们是
coming to talk about tracing in general
谈论一般的追踪
right
对
yeah like if we can come to some
是的，就像我们可以来一些
community type standards regardless of
社区类型标准，无论
the implementation that will help reason
有助于推理的实施
about these things across implementation
有关实施过程中的这些事情
so well I'm going to say I've done you
好吧，我要说我已经做了你
can come ask me questions after I turn
我转身后可以来问我问题
my mic off
我的麦克风关闭
you
您